1
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:03,000
Plain line.

2
00:00:04,500 --> 00:00:06,000
<i>Italic dialogue.</i>

3
00:00:07,000 --> 00:00:09,000
{\an8}Top-positioned line.

4
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:12,000
Two lines
in one cue.

5
00:10.500 --> 00:12.000
No hours field, dot separator.

6
00:00:20,000 --> 00:00:22,000
<font color="#ffffff">Font tag</font> and <b>bold</b>.

7
00:00:25,000 --> 00:00:27,000


8
00:00:30,000 --> 00:00:34,000
Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious antidisestablishmentarianism

9
00:00:40,000 --> 00:00:42,000  line:90% position:50%
Cue settings after the timestamp.
